It is eight o'clock.
现在是8点钟.
The children go to school by car every day,
孩子们每天都乘小汽车去上学,
but today, they are going to school on foot.
而今天, 他们正步行上学.
It is ten o'clock.
现在是10点钟.
Mrs. Sawyer usually stays at home in the morning,
上午, Sawyers夫人通常是呆在家里的,
but this morning, she is going to the shops.
但今天上午, 她正去商店买东西.
It is four o'clock.
现在是4点钟.
In the afternoon,
下午,
Mrs. Sawyer usually drinks tea in the living room.
Sawyers夫人通常是在客厅里喝茶.
But this afternoon, she is drinking tea in the garden.
但今天下午, 她正在花园里喝茶.
It is six o'clock.
现在是6点钟.
In the evening,
晚上,
the children usually do their homework,
孩子们通常是做他们的作业,
but this evening,
而今天晚上,
they are not doing their homework.
他们没做他们的作业.
At the moment, they are playing in the garden.
此刻, 他们正在花园里玩.
It is nine o'clock.
现在是9点钟.
Mr. Sawyer usually reads his newspaper at night.
Sawyers先生通常是在晚上看报.
But he's not reading his newspaper tonight.
但今天晚上他没看报.
At the moment, he's reading an interesting book.
此刻, 他正在看一本有趣的书.